<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<authentication_issue_resolution>
    <problem_description>
        Users were experiencing immediate sign-out after successful login with the message "Signed Out - You have been successfully signed out" appearing in the bottom right corner. This occurred for both admin and retailer accounts.
    </problem_description>

    <root_cause_analysis>
        The issue was caused by a mismatch between the Supabase authentication system and a custom SessionManager. The SessionManager was checking for session expiration based on its own stored data, but that data was never being initialized or synchronized with the actual Supabase session. When the SessionManager couldn't find session data, it treated all sessions as expired and triggered automatic sign-out.
    </root_cause_analysis>

    <fixes_implemented>
        <fix>
            <title>Enhanced Authentication State Handling</title>
            <description>Modified the `onAuthStateChange` handler in `src/lib/supabase-auth.ts` to be more conservative about when to set the user to null, preventing premature sign-outs during the authentication flow.</description>
        </fix>
        <fix>
            <title>Session Synchronization</title>
            <description>Updated the AuthProvider in `src/components/auth/AuthProvider.tsx` to properly synchronize the Supabase session with the SessionManager:</description>
            <changes>
                <change>Added SessionManager import</change>
                <change>When a user signs in successfully, the session is now stored in the SessionManager</change>
                <change>When the auth state changes, the SessionManager is updated with the current session</change>
                <change>When a user signs out, the SessionManager is cleared</change>
                <change>When the user data is refreshed, the SessionManager is updated</change>
            </changes>
        </fix>
        <fix>
            <title>Fixed Demo Credentials Display</title>
            <description>Updated the LoginForm component in `src/components/auth/LoginForm.tsx` to show the correct password (123456789) instead of the outdated demo password.</description>
        </fix>
    </fixes_implemented>

    <files_modified>
        <file>src/lib/supabase-auth.ts</file>
        <file>src/components/auth/AuthProvider.tsx</file>
        <file>src/components/auth/LoginForm.tsx</file>
    </files_modified>

    <testing>
        <test_point>Authentication works correctly at the Supabase level</test_point>
        <test_point>Sessions are properly created and maintained</test_point>
        <test_point>User records exist in the database with correct roles</test_point>
        <test_point>Session persistence works as expected</test_point>
    </testing>

    <result>
        Users can now successfully log in and remain authenticated without immediate sign-out. Both admin (admin@iv-relife.com) and retailer (retailer@iv-relife.com) accounts work with the password 123456789.
    </result>
</authentication_issue_resolution>
